Guide to the Frank H. T. Rhodes papers,1977-1996.
Rhodes, Frank H. T. papers, 1977-1996.
- Series IX. 1985-1986
  - Provost's Office
    - Office of the Provost
      - Vice Provost, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 18)
      - University Computing Board, 1983-85 (Box 131, Folder 19)
      - Computer Services, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 20)
      - Theory Center, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 21-23)
        ONR DARPA Site visit.
      - Cornell Abroad, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 24)
      - Johnson Art Museum, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 25)
      - Lab of Ornithology, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 26)
      - Tuition, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 27)
    - Vice Provost
      - General, 1984-86 (Box 131, Folder 28-29)
      - Career Center, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 30)
        Placement.
      - CU Press, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 31)
      - Learning Skills Center, 1984-86 (Box 131, Folder 32)
      - Science, Technology and Society, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 33)
      - Summer Session - Extramural, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 34-35)
        Telluride
      - Continuing Education, 1985-86 (Box 131, Folder 36)
      - Cornell Committee on Education and Community, 1985 (Box 131, Folder 37)
      - Cornell Committee on Education and Community, 1985-86 (Box 132, Folder 1-5)
      - Undergraduate Education, 1985-86 (Box 132, Folder 6-7)
      - Presidential Scholars Letters, 1986 (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - Cornell-in-Washington, 1986 (Box 132, Folder 9-10)
        Washington Symposium
    - Associate Provost for Equal Opportunity
      - General, 1982-86 (Box 132, Folder 11)
      - Affirmative Action Unit Representatives, 1985-86 (Box 132, Folder 12)
      - Registrar, 1982-84 (Box 132, Folder 13)
      - Equal Opportunity/Human Rights, 1982-86 (Box 132, Folder 14-15)
        Complaints
      - Office of Equal Opportunity, 1985-86 (Box 132, Folder 16)
      - Institutional Planning and Analysis, 1986 (Box 132, Folder 17-18)
      - Space Utilization and Assignment, 1985-86 (Box 132, Folder 19)
      - Language House Program, 1984-86 (Box 132, Folder 20-21)
      - Advisory Councils, 1984-85 (Box 132, Folder 22-23)
        CALS, AAP, A & S, JGSM, Engineering, Hotel, Human Ec, ILR, Law, Vet.
      - Library Advisory Councils, 1982-84 (Box 132, Folder 24)
      - Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1966-83 (Box 132, Folder 25)
      - Discontinued Centers, 1970-77 (Box 132, Folder 26)
      - Deans' Council, 1985-86 (Box 132, Folder 27-28)
      - Conflicts of Interest, 1985-86 (Box 132, Folder 29-32)
      - Music, 1982-84 (Box 132, Folder 33)
      - Salary Policy (Statistics), 1978-82 (Box 132, Folder 34)
      - Agriculture, 1985-86 (Box 132, Folder 35-36)
      - Cooperative Extension, 1985-86 (Box 132, Folder 37)
      - Industrial Extension, 1985-86 (Box 132, Folder 38)
      - Statutory Colleges, 1985-86 (Box 133, Folder 1-4)
      - Famine in Africa, 1985 (Box 133, Folder 5-6)
      - Boyce Thompson Institute, 1986 (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - College of Architecture, Art and Planning, 1985-86 (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - College of Arts and Sciences, 1985-86 (Box 133, Folder 9 -12)
      - Henry Louis Gates, Henry Louis, 1984-85 (Box 133, Folder 13-14)
      - Cornell Institute for Public Affairs, 1984-86 (Box 133, Folder 15)
      - Society for the Humanities, 1979-86 (Box 133, Folder 16)
      - College of Engineering, 1985-86 (Box 133, Folder 17-20)
      - Submicron, 1984-86 (Box 133, Folder 21)
      - Graduate School, 1985-86 (Box 133, Folder 22)
      - Black South Africans at Cornell, 1985-86 (Box 133, Folder 23)
      - Cornell University-China Exchange, 1985-86 (Box 133, Folder 24-25)
      - Professors-at-Large, 1986 (Box 133, Folder 26)
      - Regents Doctoral Project, 1974-85 (Box 133, Folder 27)
      - Business and Public Administration, 1984-86 (Box 133, Folder 28-29)
      - Hotel Administration, 1972-86 (Box 133, Folder 30-31)
    - Colleges
      - School of Hotel Administration, 1985-86 (Box 133, Folder 32-34)
        Dean review and reappointment; Statement by F. Rhodes.
      - New York State School of Human Ecology, 1985-86 (Box 134, Folder 1-3)
      - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1985-86 (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - Cornell Law School, 1983-86 (Box 134, Folder 5-6)
      - Division of Nutritional Sciences, 1985-86 (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - New York State College of Veterinary Medicine, 1985-86 (Box 134, Folder 8-9)
      - New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1985-86 (Box 134, Folder 10-32)
        Hartman, Frederick C.; letters of recommendation; abstracts; research notes; grant proposals.
    - Cornell Academic Background Material
      - Association of Governing Boards, 1979-86 (Box 134, Folder 33)
      - Association of Governing Boards, 1979-86 (Box 135, Folder 1-4)
      - Annual Reports - Other Universities, 1980-84 (Box 135, Folder 5-6)
      - Arts and Sciences Newsletter, 1980-84 (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - Carnegie Commission, 1980-85 (Box 135, Folder 8-9)
      - Publication Clippings, 1981-86 (Box 135, Folder 13)
      - Corporate - General, 1980-85 (Box 135, Folder 14-15)
      - China, 1979-85 (Box 135, Folder 16-17)
      - Education, 1979-85 (Box 135, Folder 19-27)
        Business Schools; Liberal Arts; Minority; Quality.
      - Energy, 1979-84 (Box 135, Folder 28-30)
      - Federal Funding, 1980-85 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - Financial Aid, 1979-85 (Box 136, Folder 2-4)
      - International, 1980-86 (Box 136, Folder 5-7)
      - Kiplinger Washington Letter, 1979-86 (Box 136, Folder 8-13)
      - Medicine - Health, 1979-85 (Box 136, Folder 14-17)
      - Medical Education, 1979-85 (Box 136, Folder 18-20)
      - General Interest Publications, 1977-85 (Box 136, Folder 21-26)
        Scientific Enterprise.
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1981-85 (Box 136, Folder 27)
        The Green Sheet.
      - Philanthropy, 1979-85 (Box 136, Folder 28)
      - Presidency, 1978-85 (Box 136, Folder 29)
      - Public versus Private Institution, 1980-85 (Box 136, Folder 30-31)
      - Research - General, 1978-84 (Box 136, Folder 32-34)
      - Research, 1979-85 (Box 137, Folder 1-5)
        Cornell; Federal support.
      - Science & Society, 1981-86 (Box 137, Folder 6)
      - Science & Technology, 1979-84 (Box 137, Folder 7-9)
      - South Africa, 1979-83 (Box 137, Folder 10)
      - Student Attitudes, 1979-85 (Box 137, Folder 11-12)
      - Undergraduate Education, 1979-83 (Box 137, Folder 13)
      - University - Industry Cooperation, 1978-84 (Box 137, Folder 14-18)
        Annual Report; Guidelines.
      - Values, 1979-85 (Box 137, Folder 19-20)
        Rhodes speech- Nazareth College graduation. The Dietary, Lifestyle and Mortality Characteristic of 65 Rural Populations in China.
  - Subject Files
    - Associations
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-86 (Box 137, Folder 21-24)
        Research Facilities; The Development and Utilization of International Skills; International Research; Manpower.
      - Association of American Universities, 1985-86 (Box 137, Folder 25-28)
        Engineering and Science Education; Cost principles for Educational Institutions; Rosenzweig, Robert M. statement; AAU-Fall membership meeting.
      - Association of American Universities, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 1)
        Executive Committee Meeting.
      - Association of American Universities, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 2-8)
        Annual Meeting; Executive Committee; Chief Health Officers Meeting; Membership lists.
      - American Council on Education, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 9-11)
        International Education.
      - Association of College and Universities of the State of New York, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 12-13)
      - American Association of University Professors, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 14)
      - Association of Governing Boards of Colleges and Universities, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 15)
      - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 16-19)
        Research Caucus.
      - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 20-23)
        COFHE Redbook.
      - Education Commission of the States, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 24-25)
      - Ivy Council of Presidents, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 26-30)
        Meeting notes.
      - Middle States Association of Colleges and Universities, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 31)
      - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 32)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 33)
      - Seven Universities Group, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 34)
      - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association/ College Retirement Equities Fund, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 35)
        Digest of Statistics On Higher Education In the US.
      - University Research Associates, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 36-37)
        Superconducting Super Collider.
    - Corporations
      - General, 1985-86 (Box 138, Folder 38-39)
        Chevron; Westinghouse; Ralston Purina; Peat Marwick.
      - Amoco Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - AT & T Bell Laboratories, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - Carnegie Corporation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 3)
        South Africa.
      - Corning Glass, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 4-5)
        Houghton, Amory Jr.
      - Deloitte, Haskins & Sells, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - DuPont, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Emerson Electric, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Exxon, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - General Electric, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 10)
      - General Motors, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - Hewlett Associates, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 12)
      - IBM, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 13)
      - Kodak, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 14)
      - Mobil Oil, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 15)
      - Procter and Gamble, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 16)
      - RCA, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 17)
      - Shell Oil, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 18)
      - Sohio, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 19)
      - Fellowships and Scholarships, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 20)
    - Foundations
      - General, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 21-23)
        Markey Trust
      - Prizes and Awards, 1983-86 (Box 139, Folder 24-26)
      - Atlantic Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 27-32)
      - Winifred Masterson Burke Relief Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 33)
      - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 34)
      - Dodge Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 35)
      - Exxon Education Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 36)
      - Ford Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 37)
      - Frank E. Gannett Newspaper Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 38-40)
      - Glenmede Trust Company, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 41)
      - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 42)
      - Hewlett Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 43)
      - Johnson Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 44)
        South African Consortium.
      - Kellogg Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 45)
      - Knight Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 46)
      - Kresge Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 47)
      - Henry Luce Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 48)
      - MacArthur Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 49)
      - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 50-55)
      - National Science Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 56-57)
        Site visit to Submicron.
      - New York State Science and Technology Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 58)
      - Joseph N. Pew, Jr. Charitable Trust, 1985-86 (Box 139, Folder 59-61)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Teagle Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Memberships
      - Miscellaneous Board Memberships, 1984-86 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - American Council on Education, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 5-14)
      - Association of Governing Boards of Universities & Colleges, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 15)
      - Committee on Exchanges, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 16-19)
      - Committee for Economic Development, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 20-26)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 27)
      - Department of Defense - University Forum, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 28-31)
        Science and Government.
      - Frank E. Gannett Newspaper Foundation, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 32-34)
      - General Electric - Board of Directors, 1985-86 (Box 140, Folder 35-38)
      - General Electric - Board of Directors, 1985-86 (Box 141, Folder 1-6)
      - International Executive Service Corp, 1985-86 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - Mellon Foundation Board of Trustees, 1985-86 (Box 141, Folder 8-13)
      - Tompkins County Trust Company Board, 1985-86 (Box 141, Folder 14-16)
      - Gannett Center for Media Studies, 1985-86 (Box 141, Folder 17-21)
      - Business Higher Education Forum, 1985-86 (Box 141, Folder 22-28)
      - China - Japan Trip, 1985-86 (Box 141, Folder 29-32)
      - Japan Trip, 1985-86 (Box 142, Folder 1-6)
      - Medical Systems, 1985-86 (Box 142, Folder 7-14)
        Dr. Clark Kerr, Clark's visit.
      - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1985-86 (Box 142, Folder 15-38)
        Support of early education; Economic support of Education for poor; Science and Technology; The Undergraduate Experience in America. Does College Make a Difference?
    - Higher Education
      - Continuing Education, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 39)
        Open University
      - University of the State of New York, 1985-86 (Box 142, Folder 40)
        Regent Robert Best - Southern Tier
      - General, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Bills, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 2-4)
        TAP Alert; Olmstead Legislation
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 5-8)
      - State Education Department, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 9-10)
      - Advisory Council on Postsecondary Education, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 11-13)
      - Governor Cuomo's Education Subcabinet, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      - Tax Reform, 1985 (Box 143, Folder 15)
      - Rhodes' Scholarships, 1985 (Box 143, Folder 16)
      - EMPTY, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 17)
      - Department of Education, 1985 (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Universities
      - SUNY, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 19-27)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 28-33)
    - Student Life
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 34)
      - Glee Club, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 35)
      - Incidents, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 36-38)
        Shantytown; Building occupation policy; Divestment.
      - Incidents, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 39-43)
        Stone Hall; Rhode's Letter on South Africa; Anti-Racism coalition.
      - Incidents, 1985-86 (Box 143, Folder 44-49)
        Divestment protest form letters.
      - Incidents, 1985-86 (Box 144, Folder 1-11)
    - Commencement
      - Miscellaneous, 1977-78 (Box 144, Folder 12-13)
- Series X. 1986-1987
  - Presidential/Administrative
    - Office of the President
      - General, 1986 (Box 144, Folder 14)
        Pew Memorial Trust; Heidrick and Struggles.
      - General, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 15)
        Pew Memorial Trust.
      - General, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 16-17)
      - General, 1986 (Box 144, Folder 18)
        Trip to England; Work on Darwin's Early Geological Studies.
      - General, 1986 (Box 144, Folder 19)
        List of Rhodes Memberships.
      - General, 1987 (Box 144, Folder 20)
        Halstead, Beverly.
      - General Correspondence, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 21-22)
      - General Correspondence, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 23)
      - Condolences, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 24)
      - Congratulations, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 25)
      - Congratulations, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 26-27)
        20 Years of Service.
      - Congratulations, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 28-29)
        Academic Promotions.
      - Congratulations, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 30)
        New Department Chairs.
      - Professors Emeritus, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 31)
      - Invitations, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 32)
      - Presidential Councillors, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 33)
        Purcell, Robert W.; Alberding, Charles H.
      - Presidential Councillors, 1984-87 (Box 144, Folder 34-35)
      - Presidents Emeritus, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 36)
        Corson, Dale R.; Malott, Deane W.
      - General Contact, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 37)
      - Community Contact, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 38)
      - Departmental Contact, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 39-40)
      - Employee Contact, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 41)
      - Faculty Contact, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 42)
      - Student Contact, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 43)
      - Judicial Advisor, 1986-87 (Box 144, Folder 44)
      - Judicial Administrator, 1982-87 (Box 144, Folder 45-47)
      - Judicial Administrator, 1984-85 (Box 145, Folder 1)
        Revision of Article 2, Campus Code of Conduct; Appeals Procedure.
      - Judicial Administrator, 1984-85 (Box 145, Folder 2)
        Appeals Procedure; Campus Code Violations Arising From Shantytown.
      - Parents' Letters, 1980-81 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Parents' Letters, 1980 (Box 145, Folder 4-5)
      - Parents' Letters, 1981 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Parents' Letters, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 7)
        Proposed Cuts in Federal Financial Aid.
      - Parents' Letters, 1982-84 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 9)
        Proposal from Vice President for Academic Affairs.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 10)
        Miscellaneous Sources.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 11)
        Industrial and Labor Relations.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 12)
        Human Ecology.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 13-15)
        College of Arts and Arts and Sciences Arts and Sciences.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 16)
        Engineering.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 17)
        Architecture, Art, and Planning.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 18-20)
        Agriculture and Life Sciences.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 21)
        Background Material; Letter to Faculty.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 22)
        Miscellaneous Correspondence.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 23)
        Summary of Round I Proposals.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 24)
        Rejected Proposals.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 25)
        Partially Funded Proposals.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1986-87 (Box 145, Folder 26)
        Funded Proposals.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1987-88 (Box 145, Folder 27-28)
        Arts and Sciences Proposals.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1987-88 (Box 145, Folder 29-31)
        Proposals and Worksheets.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1987-88 (Box 145, Folder 32)
        Funded and Partially Funded Proposals.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1987-88 (Box 145, Folder 33)
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1987-88 (Box 145, Folder 34-38)
        Proposals.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1987-88 (Box 145, Folder 39)
        Rejected and Funded Proposals.
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1987-88 (Box 145, Folder 40-42)
        Proposals and Worksheets, Round III.
      - Social Events, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 1)
        Gardner, Trevor C.
      - Social Events, 1986 (Box 146, Folder 2-4)
      - Social Events, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Executive Staff
      - Miscellaneous, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Senior Vice President
      - General, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 7)
        Retirement of Herbster, William G.; Post-retirement health benefits.
      - General, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - General, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 9)
        Senior Vice President Job Description and Search.
      - General, 1984 (Box 146, Folder 10)
        Internal Audit for Provost; McAdams, Alan.
      - Budget, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 11-13)
      - Budget Discussion Papers, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 14)
        Indirect Cost Recovery.
      - Office of Personnel Services (OPS), 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 15)
        Employee Attitude Survey; Welch, John F.
      - Office of Personnel Services (OPS), 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 16)
        Employee Attitude Survey.
      - Office of Personnel Services (OPS), 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 17)
      - OPS, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 18)
        Equal Opportunity at Cornell; Muka, Betty O.; Statler Layoffs.
      - OPS, 1983 (Box 146, Folder 19)
        University Policy Toward Unionization.
      - OPS, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 20)
        Exceptions to Health Insurance Coverage; Carpenter, Barry K.; Carpenter, Joyce; Barnes-Pallesen, Frances.
      - OPS, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 21)
        Smith, Robert L.
      - OPS, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 22)
        Dade, Richelle.
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1981-3 (Box 146, Folder 23)
        Rhodes Statement on Unionization; Technical Employees; Other University Presidents' Statements.
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1981-86 (Box 146, Folder 24)
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1981 (Box 146, Folder 25)
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1981 (Box 146, Folder 26)
        Fraser, Douglas; UAW.
      - OPS - Fringe Benefits, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 27)
        Child Care; CCTS.
      - OPS - Middle Management, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 28)
      - OPS - Personnel Data, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 29)
      - OPS - Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 30)
        Grievances.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 31-32)
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 33)
        Resignation of Reycroft, Lou.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 34-36)
      - Controller, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 37-39)
      - Controller, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 40)
        Business Travel Insurance; Diner's Club.
      - Budget Office, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 41-42)
        Tax Reform.
      - Budget Office, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 43)
        Gift Tax.
      - Bursar's Office, 1986-87 (Box 146, Folder 44)
      - Payroll Officer, 1986-87 (Box 147, Folder 1)
        Payroll Merger.
      - University Auditor, 1986-87 (Box 147, Folder 2)
        Student Financial Assistance Programs Audit.
    - University Counsel
      - General, 1986-87 (Box 147, Folder 3)
        Code of Campus Conduct.
      - General, 1986-87 (Box 147, Folder 4)
        Cornell Heights.
      - General, 1986-87 (Box 147, Folder 5-7)
      - General, 1985-86 (Box 147, Folder 8-10)
        Regulations for the Maintenance of Public Order; Campus Code of Conduct.
      - General, 1986 (Box 147, Folder 11)
        Statement of Student Rights; Study Group on Code of Conduct.
      - Commission to Review Campus Judicial System, 1984-85 (Box 147, Folder 12-13)
        Martin, Peter.
    - Treasurer and Vice President
      - General, 1986-87 (Box 147, Folder 14-18)
      - General, 1986-87 (Box 147, Folder 19)
        Capital Projects.
      - General, 1986-87 (Box 147, Folder 20)
        Sutter Hill Venture.
      - WHCU, 1986-87 (Box 147, Folder 21)
        Proposed Establishment of a University-owned Radio Station; Mirin, Leonard J.